// src/data/cards.js

const cards = [
  {
    id: 1,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "あ",
    reading: "a",
    back: "vowel sound a",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_a.mp3",
    due: null, // Set initial due date to now for new cards
    interval: 0, // Initial interval is 0 days
    ease: 2.5, // Initial ease factor
    lapses: 0, // No lapses yet
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "い",
    reading: "i",
    back: "vowel sound i",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_i.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "う",
    reading: "u",
    back: "vowel sound u",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_u.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "か",
    reading: "ka",
    back: "consonant-vowel ka",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_ka.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "き",
    reading: "ki",
    back: "consonant-vowel ki",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_ki.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "さ",
    reading: "sa",
    back: "consonant-vowel sa",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_sa.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "し",
    reading: "shi",
    back: "consonant-vowel shi",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_shi.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    deck_id: 1,
    front: "す",
    reading: "su",
    back: "consonant-vowel su",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_su.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    deck_id: 2,
    front: "avoir",
    reading: "",
    back: "j'ai, tu as, il a, nous avons, vous avez, ils ont",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_french.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    deck_id: 4,
    front: "語",
    reading: "yu3",
    back: "word",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_french.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    deck_id: 4,
    front: "成",
    reading: "cheng2",
    back: "become",
    audioUrl: "mock_audio_french.mp3",
    due: null,
    interval: 0,
    ease: 2.5,
    lapses: 0,
  },
];

export default cards;
